Contact

kbuse@sbcglobal.net

www.linkedin.com/in/katie-taylor-b0aa4840 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care Trauma Nursing ICU

Certifications

S.T.A.B.L.E CCRN PALS ACLS PHTLS

Katie Taylor

Flight Nurse at REACH Air Medical Services

San Francisco Bay Area

Summary

Experienced Trauma Intensive Care Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Medical-Surgical, Mechanical Ventilation, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), TNCC, and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Nursing from Mount Saint Mary's College.

Experience

REACH Air Medical Services
Flight Nurse
2019 - Present (1 year)

Stanford Health Care
Medical-Surgical/Neuro/Trauma ICU RN
July 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month)

CPMC
Critical Care RN
April 2015 - July 2017 (2 years 4 months)

REACH Air Medical Services Medical Crew Lead - Flight Nurse October 2014 - September 2016 (2 years)

Stanford University Medical Center
4 years 3 months

Medical-Surgical/Neuro/Trauma ICU RN
September 2011 - October 2014 (3 years 2 months)

Intermediate Cardiac Care RN August 2010 - September 2011 (1 year 2 months) Kaiser Permanente Telemetry/Med-Surg RN August 2008 - August 2010 (2 years 1 month)

Education

Mount Saint Mary's College BSN, Nursing · (2007 - 2008)

University of California, Davis B.A., Anthropology · (2004 - 2006)